audi.ca 2013-05-24

# Privacy > Audi Canada

Privacy Policy

It is our sincere hope at Audi Canada that what is now a purely digital relationship will evolve into a more personal one. A relationship built on trust. Our policy on privacy is simple and unwavering. We would also remind you that audi.ca is a private, copyrighted site and intended solely for personal use. And now that we've taken care of the business that our attorneys advised us had to be stated, let's get back to something more exciting, more promising: Audi and you.

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please email us at:

Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy, which explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable data may be requested.

The Information We Collect

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the audiusa.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include:

• Name  
• Address  
• E-mail address  
• Survey questions  
• Phone number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected may include:

• Name  
• Address  
• Phone number

How We Use Information

We use the personal information you provide for the purposes that we identify when we ask you to provide the information. 

We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. We may also use these e-mail addresses to provide order status and order tracking information, and to respond to queries.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services, in which case, we will use your e-mail address to provide you with these services.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and share with our advertising agencies. For example, we may tell an advertising agency that x number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that y number of men and z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to personally identify those individuals. If you choose to register or receive products or materials from us, or to otherwise give us personal information, we may store some or all of that personal information and use it for marketing research and marketing purposes, which may include sharing it with Audi Authorized dealerships or with various suppliers that provide marketing, research, or other services for us. To enhance your experience on Audi brand websites, we might use information you provide to us through your My Audi account to pre-populate forms with your name, address, phone, and email address. If you choose to save information, such as a vehicle configuration, on our website(s), we may contact you to follow up on your interest in our cars. In such cases, we may employ an outside research company to call you on our behalf.

We will never sell your personal information to any other company.

In the event of a criminal investigation or a suspected illegal activity, we may be requested by law enforcement agencies to share certain personal information.

A Word On "Cookies"

"Cookies" are small items of data that some websites either write to your hard drive upon your visit to their site(s) or store in the browser. These data files contain information the site can use to organize the pages you have visited on a particular website. Some of our websites may use "cookie" technology to measure site activity and tailor information to fit your personal interests. In this way, we can deliver tailor-made information suiting your personal interests upon your next visit to our site(s). Our use of "cookie" technology is, thus, to provide you with a more individualized delivery of information and an optimal viewing experience.

Pixel Tags

We may use "pixel tags", which are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of our websites. A pixel tag can collect information such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the tag appears; the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the pixel tag appears; the time the page containing the pixel tag was viewed;the type of browser that fetched the pixel tag; and the identification number of any cookie (please see A word on "Cookies") on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable email, we may use "format sensing" technology, which allows pixel tags to let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.

Our Commitment To Data Security

Because your privacy is important to us,  we use additional technologies and measures to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure appropriate use of this information.

 **Your Consent to Our Use of Your Information**  
You have the choice of whether or not to give us your personal information. If you share your personal information, we will tell you why we are collecting it. Certain information is required, for example, to complete your order, or to respond to your requests, as noted above. Certain information, which may be requested for marketing purposes, may be identified as optional. By providing us your information, you agree to our using it for the purposes stated. In certain places or certain pages on our website, we will ask you specifically if you wish to receive further information or to be contacted by us, or a dealer in the future. At that time, we will note and abide by your preference.

At any time, subject to legal restrictions, you may withdraw or change your consent to our use of your information, request us to delete it from our files, or notify us if you do not wish us to use your information for any purpose other than for the purposes specifically identified when you provided it to us (See How to Contact Us, below). Information collected through cookies and pixel tags may not be optional. We will inform you of the implications of withdrawing your consent.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

For your information on the e-commerce site, you can access and maintain all your personally identifiable information that we collect online by visiting the Account Information section of our website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How to Contact Us

If you wish to change your consent to our use of your information, change your privacy preferences, or update your information, or if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy,
